Hello!
It is a great privilege to be here today
As probably as much as back in '94
when I was doing a solo crossing of Alaska.
The only ‘where were you?' was those of the Yukon
river as I was skiing down before my eyes
The river began to melt ahead of schedule
And I realize I had two options, and two options only.
I give up, or I find a different way to continue.
Just like we are today.
Are we going to give up?
[Crowd] No!
Or are we going to find a different way to continue?
[Crowd] Yes!
You better believe it
So, I had to step down a couple of weeks ago
because I have a ‘step up'
And that’s what we’re asking every single one of you today.
If you are in a place where you are compromised
And you cannot speak the truth
We evaluate where you are
And make a decision to stand on the right side of history.
[Crowd] Yeah!